boatus.com 2019-12-10

# BoatUS Privacy Statement | BoatUS

Home > **BoatUS Privacy Statement**

Boat Owners Association of The United States – BoatUS – is dedicated to maintaining and protecting the privacy of our Members and web visitors, and delivering options to you regarding the use of your private and personal individual information.

### Personal Information Security

All information you provide on this site is kept secure and policies are in place for handling credit card and other sensitive information. Bank Account/Routing numbers and Credit Card information are encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and only used for authorization and payment purposes exclusively on our site. Our site is authenticated by Symantec and noted with the Norton Secured Symbol on all transaction pages as a symbol of consumer assurance that the site is safe to sign-in and make purchases.

### Controlling Your Personal Information

You may update your contact information (name, address, phone number, email & other personal information) and eMembership option by visiting [BoatUS.com/Account](https://www.boatus.com/account "BoatUS.com/Account"). Other options for contacting us to update your personal information are listed at the bottom of this policy.

### Sharing Information

If you are a Member of BoatUS we share your personal information only with companies we have selected to provide official BoatUS Member services or that support BoatUS operations including West Marine Products, Inc. We do not sell or rent Member information to telemarketers, mailing list brokers, or any other companies that are not offering BoatUS endorsed services or benefits.

If you are not a Member of BoatUS, the non-financial information you share with us may be shared with other organizations which we believe are operating in keeping with our practices and standards. You may also request to be excluded from BoatUS and partner communications.

### Third Party Practice

Should you provide personal information to any third party from our site or any other information provided to you from BoatUS, you agree that BoatUS is not responsible for the third party’s handling of your personal information. We do offer links to other sites giving you access to information that we think may be of interest to you or may benefit you in some way.

### Use and Handling of Data

Through the use of "cookies" when you visit BoatUS.com or the Members only site, [BoatUS.com/Account](https://www.boatus.com/account "BoatUS.com/Account"), a limited amount of data is stored on your computer unless you have disabled cookies in your browser. The information we collect from cookies is not comprised of individually recognizable data about you and is not usable to distinguish you personally. The use of cookies helps us track what you like the most about our site and personalize the material shown based on your preferences.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

When using our website and providing us with your information, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of our privacy policy. You should not use our site if you do not agree with this policy. We will update our policy as needed to safeguard the privacy of our Members and visitors and to keep up with changing technology. We may make these changes to the policy without providing you notice.

### Your Trust

We value your trust in us and your permission to communicate with you about how we can make your time boating more fun, easier and safer. All communications from BoatUS include a phone number, unsubscribe link, email address or physical address for you to contact us with your preferences.

You may opt-out of any future communications with BoatUS by [sending an email](https://www.boatus.com/contact/Form), calling or writing us at the following:

BoatUS  
5323 Port Royal Road  
Springfield, VA 22151
